<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book id="xr-KalpanasmatEN" indent="N" lineheight="1.5" paraheight="1.33" fontsize="42">
	<page pageno="0">
		<para>Kalpana’s mat</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="1" picjustify="right">
		<para>One day, Kalpana’s mother gave her a new mat. It had lots of beautiful colours.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="2">
		<para>Kalpana loved her mat. She slept like a log on her mat. She always had sweet dreams.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="3" picjustify="left">
		<para>Her mother said, “Take your mat with you when you go up to the hills. It will protect you.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="4">
		<para>Up in the hills, Kalpana felt very safe on her mat. No snakes or scorpions or insects came near her.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="5" picjustify="right">
		<para>But one day, Kalpana forgot to take her mat. </para>
		<para>She got lost in the hills. She was afraid. </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="6" picjustify="left">
		<para>Night was coming. Kalpana longed for her mat. Eventually, she fell asleep under a tree.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="7">
		<para>When Kalpana woke, it was morning. A little bird was singing to her. Its feathers were the colours of her mat.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="8" picjustify="right">
		<para>The little bird flew off, and Kalpana followed. </para>
		<para>She followed the little bird with the colours of her mat.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="9">
		<para>The path went in two directions. Which way should Kalpana go? </para>
		<para>The little bird showed her.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="10" picjustify="left">
		<para>After a while, the little bird stopped on a branch, and whistled. And there, below the branch, Kalpana saw her mother’s footprints! </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="11" picjustify="right">
		<para>Now Kalpana felt safe. She could follow the footprints. The little bird whistled goodbye. Then off it flew. </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="12">
		<para>When Kalpana arrived home, the people in the village were very happy. And her mother was the happiest of all. </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="13" picjustify="left">
		<para>Kalpana’s mother gave her some delicious food. Kalpana sat on her mat and ate it. “Thank you, little bird,” she thought.</para>
	</page>
</book>
