<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book id="xr-whatdalitsofoundEN" indent="N" lineheight="1.5" paraheight="1.33" fontsize="32" changetoken="20170901.161045207">
	<page pageno="0">
		<para>What Aditya found</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="1">
		<para>School was over for the day.</para>
		<para>Aditya was walking home, feeling bored.</para>
		<para>He kicked at the stones.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="2">
		<para>Suddenly, he saw a piece of paper on the ground.</para>
		<para>Eeek! It was money!</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="3">
		<para>Aditya looked around. There was nobody on the road.</para>
		<para>Nobody was watching.</para>
		<para>He put the money in his pocket.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="4">
		<para>He thought of all the things he could buy. A yummy snack? Trainers? A mobile phone? A bike? He smiled, and walked faster.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="5">
		<para>When he reached home, he showed Deeksha the money. </para>
		<para>“Wow,” said Deeksha. “But you can’t keep it. It’s not yours. We must find the owner.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="6">
		<para>The children walked back to where Aditya had found the money. Now there were people everywhere. They were searching for something.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="7">
		<para>They saw Sara.</para>
		<para>“Hello Sara. What are you looking for?” asked Deeksha.</para>
		<para>“Mr Arjun has lost his money,” said Sara. “He is very upset.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="8">
		<para>The children went over to Mr Arjun.</para>
		<para>“Is this yours, Mr Arjun?” asked Deeksha.</para>
		<para>She held out the money.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="9">
		<para>Mr Arjun snatched the money. “You stole it. You are wicked children.”</para>
		<para>“No. I found it,” said Aditya. Then the children turned and ran.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="10">
		<para>The next day, the children saw someone cycling up the road.</para>
		<para>“Oh no! It is Mr. Arjun,” said Aditya. “I am in trouble.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="11">
		<para>Mr Arjun was smiling. “Thank you for giving me my money back,” he said. “You are good children. I have brought you a present.” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="12">
		<para>He handed a box to Deeksha. She opened it.</para>
		<para>“Oh! A kite!” said the children. “Thank you, Mr Arjun.”</para>
		<para>Now everyone was smiling.</para>
	</page>
</book>
