<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book id="xr-letsbuildahomeEN" indent="N" lineheight="1.5" paraheight="1.33" fontsize="42" changetoken="20171206.160359441">
	<page pageno="0">
		<para>Let’s build a home!</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="1">
		<para>My name is Lana. I’m an architect. I’m designing a house for my baby brother and me.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="2" picjustify="right">
		<para>I've looked at homes all over the world.</para>
		<para>In some places, people have homes like tents. They fold them up when they want to move.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="3" picjustify="right">
		<para>Some people live in bamboo huts. In some places, the huts are on stilts.</para>
		<para>In some cold places, people live in igloos made of snow.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="4">
		<para>Those houses suit the places and the people. My house will suit my brother and me. I’ve drawn the plans for it. </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="5">
		<para>Now I can start building! But first I must get the space ready. I’ll need this table.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="6">
		<para>Next, I gather my materials. Houses are made from what people find around them. My house will be the same.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="7">
		<para>Some houses are built up high, so wild animals can’t get in. It makes the people who live there feel safe.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="8">
		<para>I’m building my house up high as well. We’ll be safe and cosy up here!</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="9">
		<para>A house needs to be strong. We don’t want it to fall over or blow away.</para>
		<para>I’m tying my house down with rope.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="10">
		<para>Now the walls are on! My house is nearly finished. I can’t wait to go inside, but there’s just one more thing we need.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="11">
		<para>Imagination! </para>
		<para>Look! I’ve built a beautiful castle for my brother and me!</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="12">
		<para>A house also needs a family. My brother and I play in our house all day long.</para>
		<para>Now our house is our home.</para>
	</page>
</book>
