<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book id="xr-tortoisefindsherhouseEN" indent="N" lineheight="1.5" paraheight="1.33" fontsize="42" changetoken="20171206.163553013">
	<page pageno="0">
		<para>Tortoise finds her house</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="1">
		<para>Tortoise was looking for something. </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="2" picjustify="left">
		<para>“What are you looking for?” asked Snail. </para>
		<para>“I’m looking for my house,” Tortoise replied. “Have you seen it?”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="3" picjustify="left">
		<para>“No, I haven’t seen your house. But I’ll help you look!” Snail slithered onto Tortoise’s shell. </para>
		<para>Together they searched, but they couldn’t see a house anywhere.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="4">
		<para>“What are you searching for?” Sparrow called to them. </para>
		<para>“Have you seen Tortoise’s house?” Snail asked.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="5" picjustify="left">
		<para>“I haven’t seen a house. But I’m happy to help you look!” Sparrow flew up into the sky. </para>
		<para>“I can’t keep up!” Tortoise called. </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="6" picjustify="left">
		<para>Sparrow flew down. He landed behind Snail on Tortoise’s shell.</para>
		<para>Tortoise plodded on, but there was still no sign of her house.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="7">
		<para>Mouse hadn’t seen Tortoise’s house either. </para>
		<para>She scurried up onto Tortoise’s shell.  </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="8">
		<para>A breeze was beginning to blow. It lifted leaves off the ground and swirled them around Tortoise and her friends. </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="9" picjustify="left">
		<para>The sky turned dark. “Oh, where is my house?” cried Tortoise.</para>
		<para>Lightning flashed over the hills. </para>
		<para>Drip drop drip came the rain.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="10">
		<para>The wind whipped up and whirled Sparrow and Mouse into the air.</para>
		<para>A clap of thunder boomed through the valley.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="11">
		<para>“Eeeek!” Tortoise cried. She shrank back into her shell with fright.</para>
		<para>It was warm and cosy inside.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="12" picjustify="left">
		<para>“Ah, here is my house!” Tortoise smiled. “Come and shelter beneath it!” she said to her friends.</para>
		<para>So they sat together and waited for the storm to pass.</para>
	</page>
</book>
