<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book id="xr-growEN" indent="N" lineheight="1.5" paraheight="1.33" fontsize="32">
	<page pageno="0">
		<para>Grow, grow, grow!</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="1">
		<para>“Children, I have some magic seeds for you,” said mum. “I will give you one each. There will be a prize for the best plant.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="2">
		<para>“A magic seed, mum!” said Harita. “What’s the prize, mum?” asked Aditya. “It’s a secret,” said mum, and she laughed.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="3">
		<para>Deeksha dug a little hole beside the house. She put the seed in, and put soil on top. She sprinkled water on the soil.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="4">
		<para>Harita dug a little hole beside the door, and planted her seed. “I will talk to you every day,” she said.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="5">
		<para>Aditya put his seed in his pocket.</para>
		<para>“I must win,” he thought. “I know who can help.”</para>
		<para>He ran to his uncle Ajay’s house.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="6">
		<para>He showed his uncle the magic seed.</para>
		<para>“Can you help me, uncle?” he asked. “I want to grow a big strong plant.” So his uncle told him what to do.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="7">
		<para>Aditya ran home again. He dug a little pit beside the house. He put goat manure and chicken droppings and dead leaves in it. He mixed them with the soil.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="8">
		<para>Next he put the seed in. He sprinkled water around it. </para>
		<para>Then he covered it with soil.</para>
		<para>“Grow, grow, grow, magic seed!” he said.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="9">
		<para>After one month, the plants were already quite big. </para>
		<para>“Look mum!” said the children.</para>
		<para>“I made a fence for mine, mum,” said Aditya.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="10">
		<para>Harita looked at her plant quite often. But she did not water it. And then one day … oh no! The plant was dead.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="11">
		<para>Deeksha looked at her plant every day. She watered it quite often. But then one day … oh no! The goat had eaten it!</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="12">
		<para>But Aditya’s plant grew and grew. It was a beautiful sunflower! Everyone came to look.</para>
		<para>“Well done, Aditya,” said uncle Ajay.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="13">
		<para>“So mum, I get the prize,” said Aditya. “What is it?”</para>
		<para>“Well … you all did your best,” laughed mum. “So I’ll give you all a prize.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="14">
		<para>“I’ll give you each a garden, and lots of seeds,” said mum. “But Aditya will get the biggest garden.”</para>
		<para>“That’s not a prize. That’s work!” thought Aditya. But he did not say anything.</para>
	</page>
</book>
