<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book id="xr-grandmastoryEN" indent="N" lineheight="1.5" paraheight="1.33" fontsize="42">
	<page pageno="0">
		<para>Grandma tells a story</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="1">
		<para>Grandma loves telling stories. The children love to listen. “We’re ready, grandma,” said Deeksha.</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="2">
		<para>“Once upon a time, there was a girl called Divya,” said grandma. “She lived in a hut beside the forest.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="3">
		<para>“Divya had a beautiful voice. She sang as she worked. Even the birds liked to listen!” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="4">
		<para>“One morning, while Divya was singing, a monster appeared! He had thick fur, and long arms, and red eyes.” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="5">
		<para>“ ‘Come with me, little girl,’ said the monster. He snatched Divya up, and ran off into the forest.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="6">
		<para>“Divya kicked. She screamed. She shouted. But nobody heard. Deep into the forest they went.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="7">
		<para>“Eventually they arrived at the monster’s cave. The monster pushed Divya into a cage.” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="8">
		<para> “ ‘I can’t sleep. So you must sing to me, little girl,’ said the monster.” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="9">
		<para>“Meanwhile, Divya’s brother Krishna was looking for her. ‘Divya! Divya!’ he called. Then he saw big footprints. Oh no!” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="10">
		<para>“Krishna followed the footprints. Deep into the forest he went. And then he heard beautiful singing. It was Divya!”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="11">
		<para>“Krishna crept to the cave. He saw Divya in the cage. He saw the monster, fast asleep.” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="12">
		<para>“Quietly, Krishna unbolted the cage door. Then the children tiptoed away.” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="13">
		<para>“Out in the forest, it was getting dark. The children were scared. They ran and ran and ran towards home.”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="14">
		<para>“Mum was at the door, waiting for them. They ran to her.” </para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="15">
		<para>“But suddenly, they heard loud wailing from the forest. ‘Oh no,’ said Divya. ‘The monster is crying!’ ”</para>
	</page>
	<page pageno="16">
		<para>“What happened next, grandma?” asked Aditya. But there was no answer. Grandma had fallen asleep.</para>
	</page>
</book>
